Since people always say I don't have solutions, I want to add to the post I made about the entitled Americans and their response to Hurricane Melissa at their hotels.
The solution is that you should have been helping.
The solution is that the truth of the matter is when you're a tourist, you are engaging in another culture's experience.
You are the guest.
You do not have entitlement simply because you paid to be there.
They are allowing you to be there and this they may appreciate your tourism, but nonetheless, there is an entire existence that is that exists there without you.
And if you are a human being of literally even the most basic level of civility, then you will see that in this force majeure event, what they call an act of God, the concept of tourism changes.
Because you are no longer there simply to voyeur in their experience.
You're a part of it.
And this is what's supposed to bring people together.
And so this is an opportunity to show up different.
Knowing that, yes, your dollars help the tourism, but that your kindness will help the people.
And many of you all have forgotten what it means to be the people.
And until you remember that, what's happening in your own country will continue to get more severe.
And if you think the hurricane was the storm coming for you, it's not going to be iry.
You know what y'all sound like?
Mother and the...
Sister Seals, this is your ancestor, Harriet Tubman.
Head to AmandaSeals.com and get your tickets to the live stream performance and release of my new book, What Would the Ancestors Say, on November 8th.
Also, check out When I'll Be in Your City with my book tour.
See you then.
Pop, pop.
Pop.